I have a level 102. Is that what you have? Yeah. Okay, good. Thank you everyone for being here. You know, normally this commission doesn't meet in August or July, you know, it's nice cushy job.
Um, but we noticed that, um, the three, um, hearings today all occur before our next meeting. So, you know, why not have a quick one and take care of these three? Um, so since this is a formal meeting, um, let's get some housekeeping out of the way. Uh, let's take a look at the, um, the minutes from the July 13 meeting. Um, I reviewed them, Ben.
Bobby, any questions, concerns, or if they look good, you want to make a motion and let's get those off the table? Yeah, I reviewed them as well, Alan. They all look good. Eight one-day license applications for Winter Hill. Did they ever provide any sketches for that? Side note.
Um, yeah, they did. Yeah. Okay. I sent it to you guys. That was a while ago, but yeah. Um, but besides that, I mean, it does look accurate as far as what I see. So I'm, uh, I'm, I'm good with it, Bob. Yeah. Right. I reviewed them. Uh, I reviewed them this morning and, um, everything looks great. I make a motion to accept the notes from the July 13th meeting.
I second that. Very good. Thank you, Bob. Thank you, Ben. All in favor, accepting the minutes for the July 13 minute meeting, say aye. Aye. Aye. Very good. Motion carries. Daria, nice job with the minutes. Let's go into the family network.
Caroline, do I see Caroline? Is it Lisa who's representing the MedFed Family Network? Hi, so I'm Renee. Caroline's actually in Acadia and she doesn't have internet access. I was thinking that maybe Marie Cassidy could try to jump on the call as well, but I'm here just in case, so. Okay.
So tell us about the event. By the way, thank you for the drawing. I grew up up in North Medford near Wright's Pond. We used to go to Wright's Pond, jump off Pickle Rock into the water all the time. So I appreciate the drawing of Wright's Pond. So tell us about the event. Well, I can't take credit. My husband is the drawer. So he's also the treasurer for the Family Network. So I like his.
his artistic ability. So we're hosting our annual gala, which is on Saturday, September 10th. The last time we did it was in 2019, pre-COVID, and it was always at City Hall. But we thought that this year, because of safety with COVID, and also not being limited by the number of capacity within the City Hall room,
that we decided to do it outdoors and Medford Recreation helped us set up with Wright's Pond. So it's an adult-only event from 6 p.m. to 10 p.m. with silent auction and raffles, simple fare, gave us a discount on food. So there's food, we have a band, so it's gonna be music, dancing, you know, socializing.
And the plan was to have beer and wine served by the concession stand at Rice Pond. As far as like the cups, we're having reusable plastic cups and then also some aluminum logo cups that were making souvenirs for people that bought VIP tickets.
to take home with them. So no glass. The wine would be in glass, but it's going to be at the concession. Patrons won't have any sort of glass or anything. Very nice, very nice. I hope the weather cooperates. Yeah. The rain day is Sunday the 11th, but I'm hoping it's going to be beautiful. Good, good, good. So tell me,
I see that the alcohol will be served in front of the concession stand. The stage, refresh my memory, is that where the wall is? There used to be gardens there, or that wall and the gardens are gone? It's been a while since I've been up the rights.
Yeah, it probably hasn't changed much. So there's like a wooden stage and there's maybe a little area on the front that's for, that could be for dancing, but there is some shrubbery. So the dancing, we don't even know how much dancing there'll be, but it's kind of like in a grassy knoll to the, if you're facing the stage to the right. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
Good, to me it sounds like a fun event. Again, I hope the rain does, I mean, the weather does cooperate. I don't have any questions. Bobby, Ben, anything on your mind with this? Just a question. So it is an event that you pay, you buy a ticket to go to? Yep, it's a ticketed event. We have local sponsors, Herb Chambers, Tufts,
Wegmans, East Cambridge Savings Bank. I'm gonna be forgetting some at the top of my head. So we are giving for some of our sponsors, a free ticket. But it's a two tier ticket. There's a $50 one, and then $100 VIP ticket. But it's a ticketed event.
And then there's the beach, and then there's the water. Are there enough people there to make sure somebody doesn't get drunk and go into the water? Yeah, so we'll have a police, at least one, it might be two, depending on the number of people. We're gonna have some. Yeah, so we're gonna have some police detail, and we're going to have,
Um, you know, we have some volunteers as well, but, um, we're depending on the number of people cause, um, is how many police details we need. So it's between one to two. Um, so right now I think we're about 80 tickets, but with volunteers and so forth, it probably be closer to a hundred.
We're hoping to get around 150. So I think if we get closer to the 150, we're going to have two police detail. Okay. The police detail makes me feel good because it's just, because it's at a beach and there's a possibility, you know, and it's going to be dark. I think that that's good. And then the people actually serving the wine in the, it's wine and malt, right? It's not all alcohol. Correct. It's just wine. Do you have any experience serving?
So that was one holdup that we're trying to figure out. So we do have Melanie Rayland. She has been involved with the Family Network for a while. She was a bartender for 10 years. So she did think her license may have lapsed. So she wanted to check if, one, she needed to get that sorted out before the event. Worst case, we do have a connection for someone that works at King's.
And on the side, like they have an active liquor license, they're an active bartender that we could hire them. We were just trying to save money, but I wanted to ask that about the license being active or inactive.
I'll let the Commissioner maybe weigh in on that. I was sort of, I mean, it is beer and wine. It's not a full alcohol, so that's less, I guess. And the beer is going to be in, I think, a can. It's just the wine will be in the cups. Yeah.
So I don't know that I'm saying that that's a condition that I'm necessarily strong about. I'm just trying to get a sense of the whole event. So those are actually all my questions right now. Bobby, what do you think?
I had the same concern similar to Ben when I looked at this before, and I wasn't aware that they were going to have a police detail which makes me feel good.
The, I went online and I just kind of read the details about the two types of tickets. And the $100 ticket was an open bar ticket. And where there was not, what appeared to be a licensed bartender, I think with a couple of police officers, that should be more than enough. Obviously worried about public safety. We're up to either four or five.
water fatalities this year in Medford so far. So we don't want to add to that number. But the police will be there, which will be great. And I think they'll be able to handle the security adequately that we're not going to have any issues. And that was really about my only concern. Other than that, everything looks great. I don't think there'll be an issue. Thank you for that.
Thank you, thank you. Renee, how difficult would it be to get your associates license renewed? Yeah, that's what I was thinking. I think she was worried maybe about timing, but if it's a quick thing, we told her we would, because she's volunteering her time, that the organization would help
like pay for that. So if that's something I can definitely follow up on. And if it's something that from the timeframe standpoint can get done beforehand, then we can just have her do it. Okay. You know, I appreciate Ben and Bob's input. Um, I just don't recall, you know, an outdoor event, you know, a public event like that, where beer and wine is being served and not
I should not have assurances that the people serving our license or tip certified and I just, um, I don't want to break that precedent I understand what Bobby saying well, you know, more than likely we'll have a couple of police officers on on detail and
You know, and I'm sure some of our other methods finest that might swing by when they're in the neighborhood and pop in and they're, you know, who knows, there could be as many as three, four officers walking around just watch, you know, seeing what's going on. But I, again, it may, I just feel a little more comfortable knowing that the server is tip certified or is certified or are currently certified not
you know, not, well, it expired. And so, Renee, that would be my choice or decision to have that license renewed or if it can't be renewed before the event to have this other individual come in and be the server since that individual is certified and TIP certified.
Okay, yeah, I felt the same way, just as an outsider too so I followed with Melanie Raeland and see what it takes to get her licensed and Max is giving us the link so that's very helpful. That is helpful.
Yeah, I would just say in any way we can leave it is that you will have, you know, a tip certified bartender. And if there's an issue with that, you would just let us know, you let the commission know ahead of time. So we can, you know, we still but but I believe, you know, what chairman has said is what we want, you know, that is what we want. But having someone so it's if it's either, so you may just want to make
make sure you have a backup plan. If your person has any trouble getting it, that you're able to hire, you know, I've run parties before we've hired, you know, a bartender and had a license, you know, they're a few hundred bucks. And obviously it's part of the expense, but just having a backup plan in place so that the public safety part of all of this is all met.
Okay, well, that's, that's easy I do have a. If Melanie can't get it. We do have a backup, and I'll just forward that info on so that the commission's aware of who the person is and confirm that they're licensed.
Yeah, that would be great. Um, diarrhea, I guess the 10th is a Friday, right? No, it's Saturday. So um, yeah, you have up until Friday, you know, the ninth to get you know, to reach out to diarrhea with with the name and if you don't mind, make a copy of the card because it's a you know,
like an index card, get a copy of that to Daria. So the insurance is in place. I see that you even submitted your determination letter that proves that you guys are a 501c3. So everything's there. I think to me, that's the only condition with the one day license. Yeah, so if we can get a motion, let's push this one off the table.
Sure, I can go with that. So, and then tell me if I'm missing any of this, Alan, but we'll make a motion to accept the one day license for the Medford Family Network for September 10th for the gala as proposed here with the condition that a TIPS certified bartender is working the event and Renee will let us, will provide us that information prior to the event.
Perfect. I second the motion. Very good. Thank you, gentlemen. The motion carries for the one-day license conditioned upon a TIP-certified server prior to the event. And Renee, just get it to Daria, and she'll email us, and we'll give it the thumbs up. OK, perfect. Thank you so much for your time. All right. Thank you very much. Good luck. Thank you, Renee.
Very good. Let's jump to the next one. I think I saw Nick. Did I see Nick? You did, Alan. Yes, how are you? Very good, good. Yourself? Very good. Not complaining. Thank you for the diagram. We appreciate it. So tell us a little about the event.
Basically, it's a late afternoon, very early evening music festival. They're going to have multiple bands. They've had the event in the past as well, basically over the hat shell. Again, knowing the usual turnout of these events, probably about 200 people might turn up. I think they've got four or five bands they're planning to play. So very similar to a lot of the ones we've done in the past for the farmers market, but with just more bands, I think.
Yes. Yeah. I see wine and malt. I see the insurance. Thank you. We've got the diagrams and we're familiar with the area now. There's been quite a few different events there. So we're familiar with how it's worked in the past. I don't know. Ben, Bob, any questions on this one?
Nick, you've done plenty of them in the past. You always do a great job. I don't have an issue with any of this. I'm fine with it. I agree with that. It's a good application and Nick, obviously you guys don't have any issues. How do you plan on, here's the question, we're trying to sort of master this in this area because it has a lot of events. How do you prevent, I don't know, somebody just like from having a beer and they just walk back into the parking lot? Is there any kind of signage that kind of, I mean,
We sort of understand that it's like, you don't want to keep people in a little fear circle, but is there anything that sort of prevents wandering away? Apart from us basically sort of touring around, we basically will wander about the perimeter, sort of keeping an eye on people. There's not, I mean, we basically tell people we've got to stay within this area. So the problem with that is you can't really rope it off. We haven't had any issues in the past with that.
And I think it's, but yes, I can see that there is that possibility, but as I said, we do because we're also trying to keep in good favor, obviously, is make sure there's no litter. So we actually quite often walk around looking for cups on the floor, but also checking to make sure people are staying within their boundaries. So we're also a bit, well, I'm a bit cheeky with people and say, look, you stay within the rules and we'll serve you again.
And it's so far that the audits have found that it's worked very well. Yeah, like I was thinking of a no alcohol beyond this point type of thing, you know. Yeah, actually, we can probably put some things up on there, some trees around the area, but probably it might be an idea to staple some things onto there, perhaps.
or even on a cone or anything like that. You know, I mean, really, I wasn't thinking of anything elaborate, but that was, because in the farmer's market, which is obviously it's the same venue, but it's not the same event, people kind of can like wander around within the farmer's market, holding a beer, you know, if there's nothing to sort of prevent that. And that's like where, you know, and then I was actually there once and it was like, a friend of mine walked over to me, to my car and they still were holding a beer and I was kind of like,
I guess there's no partition, they shouldn't, you know, and I was, I saw that myself. So anyway, if there, if there is, and I'll stop after this, but if there is anything that we can sort of put up that shows the parameters where alcohol, where people can have alcohol, that I believe would be a good thing to have now in moving forward. You know, when you set up at that event, at that venue.
Yeah, we can certainly work out some sort of notices, signage, we can sort of put around the perimeter, so you stick within this area. Okay. Would I be able to make a comment on that through the chair? Sure.
Um, I, just as a point of information, I was at one of the farmers markets, um, not too long ago, this in this season. And, um, Nick, you're, I would imagine that your competition went to, uh, went to Hill brewing. What they do is they have these, um, signs they're like on a H shaped wire that
The bottom part of the H goes in the ground and the top part of the H holds the sign and the sign just simply says states no alcohol beyond this point and they have it.
kind of going all around the pavilion where it's set up. And it seems like it had worked pretty effectively. Somebody has to be pretty much out of it if they're gonna walk by, you know, several signs, because he puts them in any direction that you can go. And I said, gee, that's a great idea. And, you know, just something, if you're familiar with or friendly with him, or maybe even the board, the commission can get you some information.
if you feel more comfortable with us reaching out to them, find out where we had them made, and maybe you can do the same, you know? No, actually, yeah, we've got Chummy with them. Yeah, no, that's a brilliant idea. I love it. We'll reach out to them and get some of this done. Like, there's the realtor signs, almost, that you've talked about. Yeah, almost, yeah. Yeah, the wire. It's like what the elected officials, when they're campaigning, they put those in. Very inexpensive, and it gets the job done.
It's a great point, Bob. Great point. Well, again, I guess as long as we have your assurance that there will be some kind of boundary there or some kind of notification or signs or some kind of markers, I'm fine with this. If either one want to make a motion.
Sure, I'll make a motion that we grant the license, the one day license for the event on September 18th from one to five, the music festival. And I think that's it. Just a motion to grant the license. Very good. I second. Very good. Thank you. Thank you, gentlemen.
Nick, the one day license has been approved. Again, I hope it doesn't rain. Great weather and I don't wanna jinx it, but yeah, it's been approved and just to show us that there will be some kind of boundaries there with some kind of signs or people walking the perimeter. So I thank you and good luck. Hope the event's a success.
I'm so sorry. I had one question I just actually meant to ask. Is that time correct, that one to five? Based on what I'm seeing on Facebook right now, yeah. That's the time. Yeah, Sunday, September 18th, one to five, and it's family-friendly music. Okay. Thanks, Max. Good to know. Okay. All right, great. Good. All right, take care, gentlemen. Thank you. Bye-bye now.
All right, let's jump to the last one. This is the Run MedFed Road Race. Did I see Maury? Maury, are you here? Yeah, I'm on, Alan. How are you doing? Good, good.
So will you be telling us about the event and talking? Yeah, Dave asked me to step in for him today. Basically, we are not exactly ready to, we're not sure exactly where it's going to be. We know it's September 18th. We're working on a couple of different places where this beer garden will be.
And I just, we're not prepared right now today to tell you exactly. So is there any way we can leave it open and hopefully within the next seven to 10 days, we'll be able to cross the T's and dot the I's and know exactly. Well, this inaugural year of it, there's a lot of uncertainty.
Yeah, no, you're right. You know, we do see the one day license. Thank you for, you know, it's completely accurate. We can see the million dollar insurance policy. It looks like bear only, I think was the request. So there's gonna be no wine. But what you're saying is that you guys haven't worked out the details yet as to where the area is gonna be or where the bear garden is supposed to be.
We just finished finalizing the last couple of days the exact route of the race. We've changed it a couple of times. Don't want to try to infringe too much on the neighborhoods and so forth and the churches. So we're just not sure exactly what we're going to do. Yeah. And the event is before our September meeting, because I think we meet on the 21st. OK.
Oh, Ben and Bob, what do you think? What are your thoughts on this? Is there a way that we could sort of do this in piecemeal? We could approve the one day license for bear only, but make it subject to or conditioned upon getting a final design or some kind of a drawing
and of a location of where the Bear Garden would be? Could we do it in pieces like that? Or do you guys feel uncomfortable not knowing where exactly the Bear Garden is going to be held? If I might, no, that doesn't sound bad. And Maury, hey, how you doing? Hey, Ben, how you doing? Good, good. So that's the 18th. And then what we just approved, that was on the 17th. I was just wondering about it.
that route doesn't, does it go? No, no, they're down the shell on the 17th. This is the 17th, this is the 18th, so this doesn't interfere there. So are we, are you thinking that, but do you know where the finish line is?
Probably City Hall and that City Hall parking lot in the rear and so forth. So our best guess of it right now is it's probably going to be somewhere around there. We really just haven't fully defined it. Like I said, the race path has just been finalized.
So if it, you know, if it does finish, if that's the idea, and it's finishing somewhere around City Hall, there's a lot of, that's a good location for it, in my opinion, that I feel like if we're able to see that plan, you know, prior to the event, even, you know, sooner and better is then we can just approve it. You know, I would be okay with approving it, but then we need to see a diagram that shows,
I mean, just given the fact that it's, we've done these events before. Yeah. Nothing, nothing fancy. Can you see this? This is what provides part, you know, it just, it doesn't have to be drawn by an engineer or an architect. Just, you know, just give us a good, you know, idea of the lay of the land, so to speak. Absolutely.
We're trying to find how many, what the numbers actually are. Right now there's 300 entrants into it. So, I mean, and that's going to dictate too how much space we're going to need as part of the finish and so forth like that. So we're not far away. Okay. And then who actually is put, is it the chamber or is it, who puts it on or? No, just Dave McGillivray, DMSE, Dave McGillivray Sports Enterprises.
Okay, yeah. Everyone's kind of familiar with Dave, long time Metford family and does the Boston Marathon. He did all the vaccine clinics down at Gillette and at Fenway and so forth. I mean, Dave, he handles all big events. Yeah, he does all the big events, yeah. Great job. Bobby, what say you, anything?
And no, I don't have an issue with it. Mr Chairman, the like you said you get suggested maybe would just approve it with a contingent upon some sort of a handheld drawing for a location and with the air guiding is going to be in that location anytime.
you know, up to a couple of days before the event. And then Daria, if you can, you can just email it to us. We can all review it, shoot you back a reply with an approval, and they're good to go. Yeah. Yeah, I'm good with that. Hey, Maria. Hello, I'm so sorry I'm late. I deeply apologize. Oh my gosh, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, Maria. Renee did a great job. You guys are all set. Oh, you're kidding. Renee was on? She was able to do it? Yeah. Oh my God, that's wonderful. Did she get pulled in because I didn't show up on time? Well, we don't know what goes on behind the curtain. All we know is... Oh my God. Oh, thank you so much. I was in a meeting. I'm so sorry. That's okay. So we're all set? You're all set.
It's going to be quite an event. Thank you very, very much. All right. Thank you so much. Have a great time. All right. Thank you very, very much, dear. It's wonderful. I'm sorry, Maury. Always your worry. So Bobby was saying, I agree, Bobby. I think we can do this in two pieces. I mean, we know who's running the event. We know it's right in our backyard. And we're fine. It's beer only.
I think we can do this in pieces and then we can we can get the diagram and we can do that, you know, we can sidebar that. So I agree. So I don't have any other questions. If you guys want to make a motion, that'd be great.
Yep, I can, I can do that I'll make a motion to accept the one day for the September 18 event the road run around that for road race on the condition that prior to the event we see improve a diagram of where the alcohol is being served.
And that's it. Great, thank you. I'll second the motion. Do we need to put in a rain date in case there's a rain date for that, just to cover it? Bobby, there is no rain date. It is what it is. It's my understanding that runners love rain. Don't they? People love to run in the rain, I think. So that would be good.
didn't even think of that yeah yeah no i don't like the rain i mean either all right i i thank you gentlemen um all in favor of approving the one day license with the condition that we receive uh a diagram as to where the bear garden is going to be um all in favor say aye aye yeah
Mori pass it on to Dave that it's been approved to condition upon that one piece, which is the diagram. So hope the event is a success and we hope we'll be seeing it again next year because this is its maiden
voyage, so to speak. Now, I appreciate it. We'll get that. I'll get that done sooner rather than later. So we all know what we're doing here. And as always, appreciate all your help. Good. Good. Thank you. All right. Thank you guys. All right. Take care, Mark. But I think that's a good compromise, especially if it's going to, if it's going to turn, the race is going to terminate in the city hall parking lot.
you know, that you couldn't have been a more public place. You know, so I think that that's great. So, and I think it's far enough away from the shell to you. You caught that, Ben. It is the same day, the 18th. It is the same day. Yeah. Yeah. I was wondering if I, it's funny. I just closed the other one and I don't,
So it wasn't it is on the same day. Okay. Yeah, yeah, but I think they'll be far enough away and I don't think they're going to have a running route down.
Route 16, the Mystic Valley Parkway. So, you know, that's a little too dangerous. I think they'll probably just close up the streets, the local streets to do their run or whatever. I don't know, I'm not a runner, but. And I'm sure there'll be plenty of police because of both events. There'll be, cause there'll be a lot of people moving around, walking around. I'm fine with both events at the same time. You know, I think we'll be fine. Yeah.
Good, good, good. What else? Daria, anything else on, any other items pressing on the list here? Any other business? Yeah, so I had a question. I had a grocery, Asian grocery store reach out to me and they would like to sell cooking wine called Marine. Mm-hmm.
And they wanted to see if they could sell it. So I did reach out to ABCC. But they kind of just push it on our legal counsel. Because I guess it depends on you have to look at the alcohol content or the concentration of the alcohol. I don't know if that's something that you guys dealt with before, Alan.
No, no, we know, you know, masala, you know, people cook with masala, but those always seem to be, you know, at the package stores, not in a regular supermarket. So, yeah, I don't know, I would really, it's such an odd question. We'd really have to rely on
The city would need some help on. Yeah, on a law. Yeah. Yes, the city solicitor left to so I'm gonna have to reach out to KP law and see what they say. I was away when I got the response from the state so.
Do we do we know anybody over in Malden on the Liquor Commission? The only reason why I'm asking is I've actually purchased that product before and I got it at the Super 88 in Malden over by
What do you call it? Yeah, in that plaza there. Yeah, where the little plaza is. Yeah, with social security. I don't think they have an alcohol license. So, I mean, if you did need a license for it, I'm sure the city of Malden would know if one of their places is carrying it. I had gone into several liquor stores prior to that, and nobody ever heard of it.
So they definitely don't carry it in liquor stores unless probably go to Chinatown or somewhere, then they may have it. But it doesn't taste all that strong to me. I mean, you use it in cooking Chinese food dishes and all it tastes like is like real salty, salty water. It's kind of... I think that's a good idea is to ask our counterpart in Malden if they have dealt with it.
Yeah, that's a great, that's a great idea. But I wonder if it's what Daria had said, maybe, maybe there's a, you know, the alcohol content is so small, it doesn't matter. I guess that's where I'd need a legal definition if they go, oh, it's if it's over 5%, you know, whatever it is. If it is above that alcohol content.
maybe some stores selling it, but it's not a metric, you know, I mean, I don't know. Yeah, well, that's the thing. How do we like alcohol content definitely helps, but how do we make sure that that's the alcohol content they're selling? You know what I mean? They could tell us, yeah, we're going to be like, this is the alcohol content for it. But what if they're like,
selling it, selling like a different product. I don't know. Yeah, I don't know. Well, I think it's the right thing asking. Yeah. Yeah. I think if we, if you, if you ask some questions, get, get some kind of a legal opinion, and if you could reach out to Malden, see, or Everett, see how they, how they would answer that question and then get back to us. We can, you know, we can give you an opinion.
Yeah, because Malden has a pretty large Asian population as well. So I'm sure they've come across this before. And you said, Jerry, you were calling a cooking line. Is there a specific name to it? Yes, hold on. You said like Mirin or something? Yeah, yeah. Mirin, yep, M-I-R-I-N.
Actually, if you want, I can call home and see if my wife can pull it out of the refrigerator and see what the alcohol content is. Yeah, because I tried to search it online, but nothing came up because I didn't even know. I've seen cooking wines before, but I just never seen. Maybe I just didn't pay attention that it has alcohol, but I know some people cook like white wine, so I don't. But obviously, you have to have alcohol for that, so.
Well, I mean, why from a baggage store? How you doing? Can you do me a quick favor? Can you do me a quick favor? Are you home? Could you go in the kitchen, in the refrigerator? You know that Chinese wine that's in there we use for cooking sometimes? It's got the red label.
What's that? Yeah. Is that Marin that's called? What's that? Yeah, not now. I just need you to give me some information. Then you can send me a picture if you like. I'm looking at it online. Is that the red label that says, what's the name of it, Marin? I couldn't find it.
But I got pictures of the bottles. Okay. Yeah. Okay. Yep. And we look on it and see what it's got for an alcohol content. 1.5%. Okay. Oh boy. Do you still think it's gonna.
We want the legal like definition of what is, it's gotta be a threshold. 1.5%, what? 1.5%, what? Is it, Daria, is it that store that's in the square that's kind of like at the end of the. Oh, the meet? Okay. Yeah, that's a great idea.
It's Busia Market, E-B-I-S-U-Y-A Market? Yeah, I think that's the one there. Yeah. I'm probably, I don't think I pronounced the name right, but I think you're right, yeah. Yeah, I think it's average, that's the one. It's the one next to CBS. That's interesting, I think. Spell that out for me. S-H-A-O-X.
It's funny, I don't see, I don't see alcohol content, but it says, Marin is similar to sake, but has more sugar in a lower alcohol content. So, but it doesn't say what the percentage is. Hmm. Okay. Yeah. Send me a picture and I'll call you back later. Bye.
Yeah, what they were looking at, I didn't have that, Maren, that you were talking about, Daria. The one I got was shoxing, S-H-A-O-X-I-N-G. And she said it was 1%. First she said 1.5%, but I think that was salt. Then she said it was 1% alcohol with the number 16,
with a plus sign and a minus sign under it. I don't know if that's 16% alcohol plus or minus, but she's gonna send me a picture so I can forward it to you guys. I have one here and it says 14%, to be precise, Mary. That's what it is. That's what it says, 14%. You definitely, I would say, need a license for that. Yeah, that could,
Who did you talk to over there, Daria? Was it Ralph? No, it was Bridget. Oh, you mean at ABCC? Yeah. ABCC was. No, it was Sabrina loose. I've spoken to her a couple of times before. OK.
I mean, I've got somebody over there that I know. I can give him a call. He's actually the director of the ABCC. Ralph, I don't know his last name. Yeah. No, I know who you're talking about, Ralph. Yeah. But you know, I spoke to him a couple of times. Daria, to your point about what type, because now I'm reading here,
It says they have a sweet cooking rice wine in the alcohol is less than 1%. So it sounds like it depends on what it is. It could range from this 1% to...
It's saying 14% on this one, so. So I'm wondering, should I ask Bridget, the one that reached out to me specifically, which one they wanna sell? Yes. So that we can check, we can check, we can definitely check legal. Right. To see if, depending, cause I think that would maybe help us if she presented us exactly which one she wants to sell. But I just don't know if that's like,
maybe a picture or something. Yeah. I don't know if she's going to have it on hand, if she hasn't purchased it yet, if that makes sense. She might. But what's also good about that is then we'll know what the threshold is, because if she says this is what we're going to sell and it's nine percent, then we can get a ruling and then we now know anything under nine percent is OK, but anything over that, you know, is not OK. So I think I think you're smart. I think let's speak with her and try to nail down the product and
and then we can go from there. It's such an odd question, but yeah, we'll figure it out. No, but that's good that they're asking at least because. Yeah. Could be begging for forgiveness afterwards, you know what I mean? That's true. It's not worth it. Yeah. Yeah. Very good. Anything else Daria? That was it. That was it. Okay.
Good. And I just wanted to remind you about our request, how we want to revisit some of the seating for the light. And we would ask if you, when you have an opportunity to reach out and see what the other communities are doing, how they're handling the bars versus the total. So, but other than that, this is good. So I had one thing.
that was looking at, and actually I may have, I think I have a conflict on the 21st of September for that meeting. So, I'm likely gonna have a conflict. So anyway, just, I know it can be done without me, but I don't know.
Well, I'll be around and Bob, you'll be around, correct? I'm looking at my calendar and I've got nothing on there. Nope. So I'm good. Okay. Yeah. So I will have to confirm if that ends up being a conflict, but I believe it will be. Something I've had for a while. I just can't. I don't know if I can. Okay.
So, all right, good. Well, then, let's have a, if we're all caught up, let's have a motion to adjourn. Yep, I'll make a motion to adjourn the meeting, August licensing commission. Very good, 1.48 p.m. Thank you very much. Okay, so we've given you a couple of homework assignments, Dario, so
you'll get back to us with some of the stuff before the 21st so we can look at diagrams. And then of course we can talk about the homework assignments we've given you on the 21st. Yes. All right, good. All right, cool. All right, thank you everyone. Have a good day. Thank you guys.